<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on BinaryMist</title>
    <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on BinaryMist</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 BinaryMist Ltd &lt;/br&gt;Following images are used under Creative Commons: [1](https://www.flickr.com/photos/ravefinity/12180959354/in/photostream/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/BinaryMistBlog/project/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Team Security Roadmap $2995NZ &#43; GST</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/service-development-team-security-roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/service-development-team-security-roadmap/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are security reviews and penetration testing costing you too much?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are you struggling with security defect counts being too high in the products your development teams are producing?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your competitors are beating you to market&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your customers are starting to demand higher security and protection of their data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;what-if-we-told-you&#34;&gt;What if we told you:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We could reduce the amount you spend on traditional security reviews, penetration testing, and at the same time reduce the defects being introduced, and significanlty improve your security stature, while reducing total project cost?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We could help get your product to market quicker, and with fewer security defects?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We could give you the ability to prove to your customers that you were taking the security of their data seriously, and that your product(s) were a much safer investment than your competitor&amp;rsquo;s?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;deliverables&#34;&gt;Deliverables:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let us create a roadmap for your development team(s) to follow, thus enabling them to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement the &lt;a href=&#34;https://f0.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap06.html#process-and-practises-agile-development-and-practices&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Process and Practises&lt;/a&gt;, Tools and Techniques required to take the ownership of their security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find and fix defects as they are being introduced (cheapest place), rather than late in the development life-cycle (dearest place), as discussed in Kim&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;../service-development-team-security-training/&#34;&gt;training&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide immediate and continuous visibility and measurability of the projects security stature&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ApVI7-g_wpk?start=423&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; gesture=&#34;media&#34; allow=&#34;encrypted-media&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;!-- 
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/ApVI7-g_wpk&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34; title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would get excited about similar results&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;reserve-your-consultation&#34;&gt;Reserve Your Consultation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Currently we have availability for select new clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-outline&#34; href=&#34;../../#contact&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reserve Your Confidential Consultation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Review our &lt;a href=&#34;../../tags/portfolio&#34;&gt;Portfolio&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;../../tags/testimonials&#34;&gt;Testimonials&lt;/a&gt; for some of the teams we have helped reduce costs and security defect counts by shifting the security focus up front of the development life-cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-our-customers-are-saying&#34;&gt;What our customers are saying&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andrew Balfour&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../portfolio-schoollinks&#34;&gt;Owner/Managing Director, Solvam Corporation Ltd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim Carter was engaged on a contract basis to implement and guide our future software development for School-links. www.school-links.co.nz&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In doing that he -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brought to our product a much &lt;strong&gt;higher level of expertise&lt;/strong&gt; and capability complementing our development team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directed a disciplined and methodical software development process as the Scrum Master of ‘Scrum’&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped with the restructuring and planning of our infrastructure in order to scale the product successfully&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brings &lt;strong&gt;security expertise&lt;/strong&gt; at a high level with the ability to implement &lt;strong&gt;ongoing security&lt;/strong&gt; hardening program and audits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introduced the Scrum process which provided more &lt;strong&gt;consistent and accurate&lt;/strong&gt; release cycles enabling our marketing efforts to be better coordinated and focused&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim is a good team member and we will look to reengage with his services when required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have had the unique opportunity to work in both defensive (development) and &lt;a href=&#34;../../talk/nz-js-con-2017-the-art-of-exploitation/&#34;&gt;offensive&lt;/a&gt; (penetration testing) teams, across many domains, for a large number of years. This has given us a deep understanding of what development team(s) need in order to create solutions that will effectively resist attacks from your adversaries.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/IVLpmCtiPZ0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34; title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can only take on a very limited number of roadmapping engagements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;reserve-your-consultation-1&#34;&gt;Reserve Your Consultation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Currently we have availability for select new clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-outline&#34; href=&#34;../../#contact&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reserve Your Confidential Consultation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Strategy Retainer $3495NZ &#43; GST</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/service-security-strategy-retainer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/service-security-strategy-retainer/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Not sure of how secure your business assets are?
Maybe you are thinking about establishing a security roadmap or checkpoints, but unsure of where to start, or which step to take next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may already be on the information security journey, but need some reasurance and clear direction along the way that you are investing in the areas that are most cost effective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are ways to significantly reduce the costs of security, even use security as a positive marketing avenue. Customers love it when they know you&amp;rsquo;re taking the securitiy of their data seriously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe you build software in-house and your development team(s) could do with some assistance and a sounding board to bounce their security related questions off?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or maybe you have customers that entrust their personal data to you to manage and store in the Cloud?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;how-it-works&#34;&gt;How it works&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our agreement entitles you to unlimited &lt;sup&gt;24&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;7&lt;/sub&gt; access to Kim via phone, SMS, email, Slack, Skype, Signal, Telegram, or other Instant Messaging service. I return all messages no later than the next business day, although in practice response time is usually much quicker (particularly between 9am to 6pm NZT, but also nights and weekends).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meetings are scheduled in advance, typically take place over the phone, and are sometimes supplemented with online meeting and/or screen sharing software (e.g. Google Hangouts, appear.in, Skype, etc).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are several possible areas of involvement:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regular meetings with the primary project contact to discuss strategy, longer-term issues, and business goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strategic and tactical advice based on a series of ongoing meetings with team leaders. These are individualised and mutually agreed upon. In addition, I&amp;rsquo;ll serve as a sounding board as they work to achieve their business and technical goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical review of architecture, workflows, source code, documentation, and the like. Where appropriate, I&amp;rsquo;ll provide code samples, or proof-of-concept examples. Please note that authoring shipping code, designs, or documentation is not included in this agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Situational responsiveness to needs that arise that you deem require my assistance, which are not covered elsewhere.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our fee covers four months, we arrange and pay for any necessary administrative expenses such as discussed communication mediums. Professional courtesy discounts are available for recurring annual arrangements. Participation is extremely limited. You can elect to be added to the waiting list if spots are not available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;reserve-your-consultation&#34;&gt;Reserve Your Consultation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Currently we have availability for select new clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-outline&#34; href=&#34;../../#contact&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reserve Your Confidential Consultation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Security into Your Development Teams (workshop) $500 &#43; GST per student</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/service-development-team-security-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/service-development-team-security-training/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Few organisations understand the &lt;a href=&#34;../../talk/all-day-devops--talk-secrets-of-a-high-performance-security-focussed-agile-team&#34;&gt;secrets&lt;/a&gt; of shifting the focus on security from late in the software development life-cycle to within the Development Team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only does this significantly reduce the number of security defects being pushed to your production systems, but also significantly reduces the total cost of development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;cheapest-place-https-f0-holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers-com-chap06-html-leanpub-auto-cheapest-place-to-deal-with-defects-to-deal-with-defects&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://f0.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap06.html#leanpub-auto-cheapest-place-to-deal-with-defects&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Cheapest place&lt;/a&gt; to deal with defects&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There have been many studies specifically looking at the costs of finding and fixing defects early, as opposed to the planning of how to fix defects once the product is delivered, or not planning at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following table shows the average cost of fixing defects based on when they were introduced versus when they are detected. Putting these practises in the right order can reduce costs of fixing security defects by up to 100 times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://f0.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap06.html#leanpub-auto-cheapest-place-to-deal-with-defects&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../img/project/AverageCostOfFixingDefects.png&#34; alt=&#34;average cost of fixing defects&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So&amp;hellip; by simply shifting the security expertise from the end of the project to within the development team, thus enabling developers to find and fix their defects as they are being introduced, huge cost savings can be enjoyed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not as difficult as you may think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;on-the-day&#34;&gt;On the Day&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim will lead the class through the tools, techniques and thought processes of both red (attacking) and blue (defending) teams along with how to combine these attributes into the purple team focussing on security, productivity, and tasked with continuously delivering sustainable maintainable technical solutions to market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34; style=&#34;padding-top: 10px&#34;&gt;
   &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-1&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-10&#34; style=&#34;padding-top: 10px&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
         &lt;div class=&#34;col-xs-12 col-sm-3 pub-row-heading&#34; style=&#34;line-height:34px; font-weight:bold;&#34;&gt;Location&lt;/div&gt;
         &lt;div class=&#34;col-xs-12 col-sm-9&#34;&gt;At your venue&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34; style=&#34;padding-top: 10px&#34;&gt;
         &lt;div class=&#34;col-xs-12 col-sm-3 pub-row-heading&#34; style=&#34;line-height:34px; font-weight:bold;&#34;&gt;Links&lt;/div&gt;
         &lt;div class=&#34;col-xs-12 col-sm-9&#34;&gt;
            &lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-outline&#34; href=&#34;../../files/talk//BuildingSecurityIntoYourDevTeams-Generic.pdf&#34;&gt;PDF&lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-outline&#34; href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/BinaryMistBlog/publication/holistic-infosec-for-web-developers/&#34;&gt;Source Book Series&lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-outline&#34; href=&#34;../../tags/workshops&#34;&gt;Kim&amp;rsquo;s other Workshops&lt;/a&gt;
         &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-1&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim will explain the roles of &amp;rsquo;T&amp;rsquo; shaped professionals, including placement of security champions to create your purple Development Teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will work through how to implement the Sensible Security Model (SSM) within each and every Sprint, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating actionable countermeasure Product Backlog Items&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrating them into the same Product Backlog that your Development Team has been pulling business focussed items from&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ordering them based on the risk ratings you create for each&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../img/project/Countermeasures-Backlog.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;countermeasures backlog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim will discuss how and where Agile Development Teams often fail, along with how to succeed with security with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://f0.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap06.html#leanpub-auto-how-and-why-many-software-development-shops-fail&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;familiar anecdote&lt;/a&gt;. Then augmenting your Scrum process within each and every Sprint, with a collection of development focussed &lt;a href=&#34;http://f0.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap06.html#process-and-practises-agile-development-and-practices&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;processes and practises&lt;/a&gt;, tools and techniques that have proven their value at drastically reducing defects before production deployment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim will walk us through the SSM threat modelling process with theory and hands on exercises in areas such as Physical, People, VPS, Network, Cloud and Web Applications. Including sub topics such as Docker, &lt;a href=&#34;https://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap05.html#cloud-countermeasures-serverless&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Serverless&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;../../talk/isig-2017-workshop-windows-exploitation-and-persistence-with-ps/&#34;&gt;PowerShell&lt;/a&gt; and many others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../img/project/SSM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;countermeasures backlog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;more-detail-h4&#34;&gt;More Detail&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Training material will be augmented with Extracts from Kim&amp;rsquo;s interviews on Software Engineering Radio with security experts such as Diogo Mónica (&lt;a href=&#34;../../publication/ser-podcast-docker-security/&#34;&gt;Docker Security&lt;/a&gt; Team Lead) and &lt;a href=&#34;../../publication/ser-podcast-network-security&#34;&gt;Haroon Meer&lt;/a&gt; (creator of Canary tools and tokens).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Each student will receive &lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt; copies of the first two parts of Kim&amp;rsquo;s book series &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;../../publication/holistic-infosec-for-web-developers/&#34;&gt;Holistic Info-Sec for Web Developers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo; (weighing in at approximately 700 pages) which this training is based on, as companion course material to accompany the training, to assist with ongoing self learning, and as a valuable reference resource long after the training has finished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Minimum of four students per workshop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;learnings&#34;&gt;Learnings&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coverage of topic chapters:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://f0.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap07.html#physical&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Physical&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://f0.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap08.html#people&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap03.html#vps&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;VPS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap04.html#network&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap05.html#cloud&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap06.html#web-applications&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Web Applications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-others-are-saying&#34;&gt;What others are saying&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&#34;twitter-tweet&#34;&gt;&lt;p lang=&#34;en&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Enjoying the variety in &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/binarymist?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;@binarymist&lt;/a&gt; ‘s training today. So much content :) &lt;a href=&#34;https://t.co/OWKAFKFwu2&#34;&gt;pic.twitter.com/OWKAFKFwu2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Kylie (@kylieengineer) &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/kylieengineer/status/923342793405165569?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;October 26, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src=&#34;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;reserve-your-workshop&#34;&gt;Reserve Your Workshop&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Currently we have availability for select new clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-outline&#34; href=&#34;../../#contact&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reserve Your Confidential Consultation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christchurch Hacker Con</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/external-project-chcon2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/external-project-chcon2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numisec Pte.</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/portfolio-numisec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/portfolio-numisec/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Security Review - Node.js Microservices&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
   &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left; width: 50%&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../img/portfolio/Numisec.1.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;
         Security Review of clients (bank in jakarta) Dockerised NodeJS microservices.
         &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
         Common Technologies:
         &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
         &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Node.js 8.5&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;hapi, joi&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Docker&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;OpenShift&lt;/li&gt;
         &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See &lt;a href=&#34;../testimonial-stefan-streichsbier&#34;&gt;testimonial&lt;/a&gt; by Stefan Streichsbier&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stefan Streichsbier</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/testimonial-stefan-streichsbier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/testimonial-stefan-streichsbier/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;testimonial-img-bordered&#34; src=&#34;../../img/testimonials/StefanStreichsbier.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../portfolio-numisec&#34;&gt;Numisec Pte. Ltd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve met Kim at DevSecCon Singapore in 2017 where he gave a well-received &lt;a href=&#34;../../talk/devseccon-asio-2017-developing-a-high-perf-security-focussed-agile-team/&#34;&gt;workshop&lt;/a&gt;. A few months later we had a project where his top-notch strong &lt;strong&gt;Node.js security&lt;/strong&gt; code review skills were required and this gave us the chance to work together closely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over a 2 week period he was doing security code reviews of containerized Node.js &lt;strong&gt;microservices&lt;/strong&gt; in a very thorough way. We communicated well and progressed quickly. Kim has a very broad yet deep understanding of modern application security that comes from years of experience. I can recommend Kim to anyone who needs an &lt;a href=&#34;https://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap06.html#web-applications&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;application security&lt;/a&gt; expert and wants a professional second opinion on the security posture of an application.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobiddiction</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/portfolio-mobiddiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/portfolio-mobiddiction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DevOps Implementation and Security Review&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
   &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left; width: 50%&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../img/portfolio/Mobiddiction.1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;
         Provided security review, devops review, support, detailed road map and Product Backlog detailing path along with work items to improvement.
         &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
         Set-up Process and Practises to introduce higher quality within development teams.
         &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
         Increase speed of Software/Product delivery.
         &lt;br&gt;
         Automation of monitoring and actions on various AWS components.
      &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Established culture, tools and techniques across the development teams:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Security Regression Testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Static analysis, Cyclomatic complexity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuous Integration (Jenkins, CircleCI)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pair Review and Programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additional details on Kim&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/carterkim/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP New Zealand Day</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/external-project-owaspnzday2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/external-project-owaspnzday2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Montgomery</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/testimonial-peter-montgomery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/testimonial-peter-montgomery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;testimonial-img-bordered&#34; src=&#34;../../img/testimonials/PeterMontgomery.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../portfolio-inventorytech&#34;&gt;Founder and CEO, InventoryTech Limited&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim provided us with excellent support services during a development transition with our cloud software services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim is a highly capable software developer with deep experience and capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recommend Kim&amp;rsquo;s services, he did a great job for us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MYOB</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/portfolio-myob/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/portfolio-myob/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DevSecOps and AWS Migration&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
   &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left; width: 50%&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.myob.com/nz/enterprise/software-systems/payglobal/employee-self-service-portal&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../img/portfolio/Myob.1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;
         Implemented Security Regression Test framework based on Kim&#39;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/binarymist/NodeGoat/wiki/Security-Regression-Testing-with-Zap-API&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Proof of Concept&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

         Re-architected legacy to new code-base.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

         Migrated PayGlobal services to AWS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

         Scrum mentoring.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

         Additional details on Kim&#39;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/carterkim/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lana Winders</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/testimonial-lana-winders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/testimonial-lana-winders/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;testimonial-img-bordered&#34; src=&#34;../../img/testimonials/LanaWinders.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../portfolio-sbs&#34;&gt;General Manager, SBS Bank&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed having Kim as part of our team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have done a fantastic job there and we are lucky to have you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rachel Robertson</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/testimonial-rachel-robertson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/testimonial-rachel-robertson/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;testimonial-img-bordered&#34; src=&#34;../../img/testimonials/NoImage.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../portfolio-sbs&#34;&gt;Project Manager, SBS Bank&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Cheers to Kim on our first PIB change completed in house.&lt;br&gt;
The PIB reskin looks magnificent and has gone through without a glitch Well done Kim – you’ve given SBS that little bit of independence and it feels fantastic!&lt;br&gt;
hope you feel really proud Kim.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Team Security Implementation</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/service-development-team-security-implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/service-development-team-security-implementation/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve realised that you need to do something about the rising number of defects being introduced into your software products. Competetors are out-manouvering you. Security reviews and penetration testing is costing you too much. Your customers are demanding higher security and protection of their data. Your development team(s) simply don&amp;rsquo;t have the time or expertise to add more security process and practises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;what-if-we-told-you&#34;&gt;What if we told you:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We could reduce the amount you spend on traditional security reviews, penetration testing, and at the same time reduce the defects being introduced, and significanlty improve your security stature, while reducing total project cost?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We could help get your product to market quicker, and with fewer security defects?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We could give you the ability to prove to your customers that you were taking the security of their data seriously, and that your product(s) were a much safer investment than your competitor&amp;rsquo;s?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You could even invite your customers to be part of your development process, and be amazed by seeing security defects fixed as they are found in a continuous integratioin or nightly build environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;deliverables&#34;&gt;Deliverables:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have a &lt;a href=&#34;../service-development-team-security-roadmap/&#34;&gt;roadmap&lt;/a&gt;, which Kim can provide at a fixed price, detailing where your development team(s) could be doing better, how to do better, and providing clear steps to achieve the shared goal, teams will often need some hands on help to establish the processes and practises, tools and techniques outlined in the &lt;a href=&#34;project/service-development-team-security-roadmap/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;roadmap&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;../service-development-team-security-training/&#34;&gt;workshop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim can help your development team(s) with the implementation of the security roadmap, provide ongoing mentoring if required, and then hand the reins over, or continue to offer ongoing &lt;a href=&#34;../service-security-strategy-retainer/&#34;&gt;advice&lt;/a&gt; and mentoring, this way setting you up for success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily take a long time to implement, and has the side-effect of saving huge amounts of money on fixing defects once they&amp;rsquo;ve been in the system for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would get excited about reducing costs on security, while increasing the ability of your development team(s) to deliver secure products&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;reserve-your-consultation&#34;&gt;Reserve Your Consultation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Currently we have availability for select new clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-outline&#34; href=&#34;../../#contact&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reserve Your Confidential Consultation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Review our &lt;a href=&#34;../../tags/portfolio&#34;&gt;Portfolio&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;../../tags/testimonials&#34;&gt;Testimonials&lt;/a&gt; for some of the teams we have helped reduce costs and security defect counts by shifting the security focus up front of the development life-cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-our-customers-are-saying&#34;&gt;What our customers are saying&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andrew Balfour&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../portfolio-schoollinks&#34;&gt;Owner/Managing Director, Solvam Corporation Ltd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim Carter was engaged on a contract basis to implement and guide our future software development for School-links. www.school-links.co.nz&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In doing that he -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brought to our product a much &lt;strong&gt;higher level of expertise&lt;/strong&gt; and capability complementing our development team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directed a disciplined and methodical software development process as the Scrum Master of ‘Scrum’&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped with the restructuring and planning of our infrastructure in order to scale the product successfully&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brings &lt;strong&gt;security expertise&lt;/strong&gt; at a high level with the ability to implement &lt;strong&gt;ongoing security&lt;/strong&gt; hardening program and audits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introduced the Scrum process which provided more &lt;strong&gt;consistent and accurate&lt;/strong&gt; release cycles enabling our marketing efforts to be better coordinated and focused&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim is a good team member and we will look to reengage with his services when required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have had the unique opportunity to work in both defensive (development) and &lt;a href=&#34;../../talk/nz-js-con-2017-the-art-of-exploitation/&#34;&gt;offensive&lt;/a&gt; (penetration testing) teams, across many domains, for a large number of years. This has given us a deep understanding of what development team(s) need in order to create solutions that will effectively resist attacks from your adversaries.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/IVLpmCtiPZ0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34; title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can only take on one or two of these engagements every few months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;reserve-your-consultation-1&#34;&gt;Reserve Your Consultation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Currently we have availability for select new clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-outline&#34; href=&#34;../../#contact&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reserve Your Confidential Consultation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Review, Penetration Testing</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/service-security-review-penetration-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/service-security-review-penetration-testing/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;situation&#34;&gt;Situation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your software project is at the stage where you would like some verification that it is going to be able to resist attacks from your likely attackers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have deployed your project to the Cloud and need some confirmation that the infrastructure is configured correctly so that your attackers can not compromise your customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Docker containers can be a god send for creating micro-service architectures, but often Docker environments are insecure by default.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your Software Engineers are building networks by way of infrastructure as code (IaC). These networks need security review and sometimes penetration testing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;we-can-do-better&#34;&gt;We can do better&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would you like peace of mind that your software project is going to be able to withstand the likely attacks from your adversaries?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Achieving and maintaining a level of security with your cloud configuration, security rules and settings can be a daunting task. Would you like to be able to relax and be confident that this is taken care of?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Securing your micro-service and Docker environments is not for the faint hearted, this is an area that Kim has a wealth of experience in. You too can share the same knowledge that your micro-service and Docker environments are well secured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the knowledge and experience that we have with cloud environments and tools such as Terraform, Ansible, etc, you can rest assured that the networks your Engineers are creating are configured correctly, and will resist the attempts of your attackers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-we-can-help&#34;&gt;How we can help&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although we advocate bringing the security focus &lt;a href=&#34;../../project/service-development-team-security-implementation/&#34;&gt;up front&lt;/a&gt; where it&amp;rsquo;s the cheapest to implement, for some organisations, this takes time to get to this point. We would like to help you get there, but in the interim, we can help you with reviewing, testing and establishing a solid security stature across your products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim can review, penetration test, provide a custom report outlining the defects and effective mitigations. Kim can also apply the mitigations or if you prefer, work with your development team(s) to help them understand the issues and how to apply the mitigations themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can traverse the mine field of your cloud environment for you, locate, document, work with your Engineers to rectify any security issues in your cloud environments, or apply the necessary remedies for you and your teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim is able to review, test, evaluate costs and trade-offs, document, and inform you of areas that could be improved, and then go ahead and apply the necessary improvements, or simply coach your development teams on how to apply the security mitigations and improvements, so that this becomes second nature for your Engineers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Network security is an area that Kim has been actively engaged in designing, building and breaking for many years. Let Kim apply his knowledge and experience to your project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let us review, test, and provide the peace of mind that your products will withstand the attacks from your adversaries&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;reserve-your-consultation&#34;&gt;Reserve Your Consultation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Currently we have availability for select new clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-outline&#34; href=&#34;../../#contact&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reserve Your Confidential Consultation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the sensitive nature of these engagements, they are not usually added to our portfolio, but you can see&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-our-customers-are-saying&#34;&gt;What our customers are saying&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stefan Streichsbier&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../portfolio-numisec&#34;&gt;Numisec Pte. Ltd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve met Kim at DevSecCon Singapore in 2017 where he gave a well-received &lt;a href=&#34;../../talk/devseccon-asio-2017-developing-a-high-perf-security-focussed-agile-team/&#34;&gt;workshop&lt;/a&gt;. A few months later we had a project where his top-notch strong &lt;strong&gt;Node.js security&lt;/strong&gt; code review skills were required and this gave us the chance to work together closely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over a 2 week period he was doing security code reviews of containerized Node.js &lt;strong&gt;microservices&lt;/strong&gt; in a very thorough way. We communicated well and progressed quickly. Kim has a very broad yet deep understanding of modern application security that comes from years of experience. I can recommend Kim to anyone who needs an &lt;a href=&#34;https://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap06.html#web-applications&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;application security&lt;/a&gt; expert and wants a professional second opinion on the security posture of an application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim has spent significant effort in researching Docker security, how to determine insecure environments, configurations, how to provide countermeasures, and has &lt;a href=&#34;https://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap03.html#vps-identify-risks-docker&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;written&lt;/a&gt; on the topic &lt;a href=&#34;https://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap03.html#vps-countermeasures-docker&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;extensively&lt;/a&gt;. Kim has also liaised with and &lt;a href=&#34;../../publication/ser-podcast-docker-security/&#34;&gt;interviewed&lt;/a&gt; the Docker Security Team Lead, and is well equipped to address and rectify any security issues you may have with Docker environments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;BinaryMist project leveraging Docker and Terrafrom to create free and secure networking components:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/binarymist/aws-docker-host&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://github.com/binarymist/aws-docker-host/raw/master/Logo.png&#34; alt=&#34;AWS Docker Host&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim has also detailed some of his network knowledge in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap04.html#network&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Network chapter&lt;/a&gt; of his second book, along with &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/BinaryMistBlog/publication/ser-podcast-network-security/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;interview&lt;/a&gt; of network security guru Haroon Meer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because Kim has spent many years in development and engineering, as well as performing security reviews and penetration tests, he has a unique and holistic view of what is required from both sides (defence and attack), so is able to provide effective and realistic simulations of real-world attackers and at the same time, coach developers what to look for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the nature of this type of work, we can only take on one new client per month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;reserve-your-consultation-1&#34;&gt;Reserve Your Consultation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Currently we have availability for select new clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-primary btn-outline&#34; href=&#34;../../#contact&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reserve Your Confidential Consultation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InventoryTech</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/portfolio-inventorytech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/BinaryMistBlog/project/portfolio-inventorytech/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Transitioning, architecture and development&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
   &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left; width: 50%&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://clevermedkits.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../img/portfolio/clevermedkit.1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;
         
Assisted with transition between engineering teams.&lt;br&gt;
Provided architecture and development assistance.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Technologies:
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
   &lt;li&gt;NodeJS, MongoDB&lt;/li&gt;
   &lt;li&gt;BackboneJS, MarionetteJS, Gulp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
Platforms:
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
   &lt;li&gt;Heroku&lt;/li&gt;
   &lt;li&gt;AWS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See &lt;a href=&#34;../testimonial-peter-montgomery&#34;&gt;testimonial&lt;/a&gt; by Peter Montgomery&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
