<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on BinaryMist</title>
    <link>https://binarymist.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on BinaryMist</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 BinaryMist Ltd &lt;/br&gt;Following images are used under Creative Commons: [1](https://www.flickr.com/photos/ravefinity/12180959354/in/photostream/) &lt;/br&gt;[Privacy](/publication/privacy/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://binarymist.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Team Security Teardown $995NZ &#43; GST</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/service-development-team-security-teardown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/service-development-team-security-teardown/</guid>
      <description>There are often many issues with any given Development Teams process, such as the following points:
 The way the individuals communicate Obstacles that slow the Team down unnecessarily Waiting on information and decisions from people outside of the team Team members getting asked to do tasks not on the critical path Lack of autonomy lack of necessary skills and knowledge to create robust, scalable, extensible, maintainable, and secure systems High level of multi-tasking Low morale due to many issues Many others  Similarly there can be many technical issues that negatively affect the rapid development of the type of software solution you are trying to get to market, such as:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Team Security Roadmap $2995NZ &#43; GST</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/service-development-team-security-roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/service-development-team-security-roadmap/</guid>
      <description>Are security reviews and penetration testing costing you too much? Are you struggling with security defect counts being too high in the products your development teams are producing? Your competitors are beating you to market Your customers are starting to demand higher security and protection of their data  What if we told you: That by working with you we could reduce the amount you spend on traditional security reviews, penetration testing, and at the same time reduce the defects being introduced, and significantly improve your security stature, while reducing total project cost?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Strategy Retainer $3495NZ &#43; GST</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/service-security-strategy-retainer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/service-security-strategy-retainer/</guid>
      <description>Not sure of how secure your business assets are? Maybe you are thinking about establishing a security roadmap or checkpoints, but unsure of where to start, or which step to take next.
You may already be on the information security journey, but need some reassurance and clear direction along the way that you are investing in the areas that are most cost effective.
There are ways to significantly reduce the costs of security, even use security as a positive marketing avenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Security into Your Development Teams (workshop) $500 &#43; GST per student</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/service-development-team-security-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/service-development-team-security-training/</guid>
      <description>Few organisations understand the secrets of shifting the focus on security from late in the software development life-cycle to within the Development Team.
Not only does this significantly reduce the number of security defects being pushed to your production systems, but also significantly reduces the total cost of development.
Cheapest place to deal with defects There have been many studies specifically looking at the costs of finding and fixing defects early, as opposed to the planning of how to fix defects once the product is delivered, or not planning at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christchurch Hacker Con</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/external-project-chcon2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/external-project-chcon2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numisec Pte.</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-numisec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-numisec/</guid>
      <description>Security Review - Node.js Microservices
    Security Review of clients (bank in jakarta) Dockerised NodeJS microservices. Common Technologies:  Node.js 8.5 hapi, joi Docker OpenShift     See testimonial by Stefan Streichsbier</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stefan Streichsbier</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-stefan-streichsbier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-stefan-streichsbier/</guid>
      <description>Numisec Pte. Ltd
 I&amp;rsquo;ve met Kim at DevSecCon Singapore in 2017 where he gave a well-received workshop. A few months later we had a project where his top-notch strong Node.js security code review skills were required and this gave us the chance to work together closely.
Over a 2 week period he was doing security code reviews of containerized Node.js microservices in a very thorough way. We communicated well and progressed quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobiddiction</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-mobiddiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-mobiddiction/</guid>
      <description>DevOps Implementation and Security Review
    Provided security review, devops review, support, detailed road map and Product Backlog detailing path along with work items to improvement. Set-up Process and Practises to introduce higher quality within development teams. Increase speed of Software/Product delivery. Automation of monitoring and actions on various AWS components.    Established culture, tools and techniques across the development teams:
 Security Regression Testing Static analysis, Cyclomatic complexity Continuous Integration (Jenkins, CircleCI) Pair Review and Programming  Additional details on Kim&amp;rsquo;s LinkedIn</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWASP New Zealand Day</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/project-owaspnzday2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/project-owaspnzday2018/</guid>
      <description>Workshop As well as the main conference on Monday, we are pleased to be able to provide training on Sunday at the same venue. All details in the workshop listed below.
Main Event We are proud to announce the ninth OWASP New Zealand Day conference, held at the University of Auckland on Monday February 5th, 2018. OWASP New Zealand Day is a one-day conference dedicated to information security, with an emphasis on secure architecture and development techniques to help developers build more secure applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Montgomery</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-peter-montgomery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-peter-montgomery/</guid>
      <description>Founder and CEO, InventoryTech Limited
 Kim provided us with excellent support services during a development transition with our cloud software services.
Kim is a highly capable software developer with deep experience and capabilities.
I recommend Kim&amp;rsquo;s services, he did a great job for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MYOB</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-myob/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-myob/</guid>
      <description> DevSecOps and AWS Migration
    Implemented Security Regression Test framework based on Kim&#39;s Proof of Concept
Re-architected legacy to new code-base.
Migrated PayGlobal services to AWS.
Scrum mentoring.
Additional details on Kim&#39;s LinkedIn
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lana Winders</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-lana-winders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-lana-winders/</guid>
      <description>General Manager, SBS Bank
 I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed having Kim as part of our team.
You have done a fantastic job there and we are lucky to have you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rachel Robertson</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-rachel-robertson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-rachel-robertson/</guid>
      <description>Project Manager, SBS Bank
 Congratulations!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Cheers to Kim on our first PIB change completed in house.
The PIB reskin looks magnificent and has gone through without a glitch Well done Kim – you’ve given SBS that little bit of independence and it feels fantastic!
hope you feel really proud Kim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Team Security Implementation</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/service-development-team-security-implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/service-development-team-security-implementation/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve realised that you need to do something about the rising number of defects being introduced into your software products. Competitors are outmanoeuvring you. Security reviews and penetration testing is costing you too much. Your customers are demanding higher security and protection of their data. Your Development Team(s) simply don&amp;rsquo;t have the time or expertise to add more heavy weight security process and practises.
What if we told you: That by working with you we could reduce the amount you spend on traditional security reviews, penetration testing, and at the same time reduce the defects being introduced, and significantly improve your security stature, while reducing total project cost?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Review, Penetration Testing</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/service-security-review-penetration-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/service-security-review-penetration-testing/</guid>
      <description>Situation Your software project is at the stage where you would like some verification that it is going to be able to resist attacks from your likely attackers.
You have deployed your project to the Cloud and need some confirmation that the infrastructure is configured correctly so that your attackers can not compromise your customers.
Docker containers can be a god send for creating micro-service architectures, but often Docker environments are insecure by default.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InventoryTech</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-inventorytech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-inventorytech/</guid>
      <description>Transitioning, architecture and development
    Assisted with transition between engineering teams.
Provided architecture and development assistance. Technologies:  NodeJS, MongoDB BackboneJS, MarionetteJS, Gulp  Platforms:  Heroku AWS     See testimonial by Peter Montgomery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lentune</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-lentune/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-lentune/</guid>
      <description> Architectural and Security Consulting
    Provided architectural, engineering and security guidance to the Wholesaler development team.
Migrated parts of the C#.Net solution to a CQRS approach.
Large cost savings.    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Gadsby</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-david-gadsby/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-david-gadsby/</guid>
      <description>Principal Recruitment Consultant, Platinum Recruitment Ltd
 We engaged Kim to take the technical reigns on a large client project.
Kim was on point right from day one, diving head first into the work and committing himself to project delivery. Technically, Kim is very sharp with a good head for commercial software development. If there’s something strange in your development project, forget the Ghostbusters and give Kim Carter a call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBS Bank</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-sbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-sbs/</guid>
      <description>Personal Internet Banking
    Successfully brought the development of Personal Online-Banking in-house. Assisted in recruiting and mentoring managers and a development team to take over PIB. Created road map for ongoing architecture and development. Restructured and worked on new features. Ongoing reviews and security status reports with proposed solutions. Full evaluation of web module loaders. Replacing RequireJS with WebPack to utilise all module systems available (ES6 modules, globals, AMD, CommonJS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Balfour</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-andrew-balfour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-andrew-balfour/</guid>
      <description>Owner/Managing Director, Solvam Corporation Ltd
 Kim Carter was engaged on a contract basis to implement and guide our future software development for School-links. www.school-links.co.nz
In doing that he -
 Brought to our product a much higher level of expertise and capability complementing our development team Directed a disciplined and methodical software development process as the Scrum Master of ‘Scrum’ Helped with the restructuring and planning of our infrastructure in order to scale the product successfully Brings security expertise at a high level with the ability to implement ongoing security hardening program and audits Introduced the Scrum process which provided more consistent and accurate release cycles enabling our marketing efforts to be better coordinated and focused  Kim is a good team member and we will look to reengage with his services when required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School-Links</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-schoollinks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-schoollinks/</guid>
      <description>Process Improvement. Back End Re-Architect
    Architected and re-factored school-links, a PHP messaging system into NodeJS. Security reviews - hardening of applications and infrastructure (multi platform environment). Linux System administration and DevOps. Mentoring, setting up and mastering another Scrum Team. Re-factored enterprise LAMP application to full stack modular JavaScript enterprise application. Jenkins evaluation. Set-up coding standards, conventions and guidelines.    Common Technologies:
 Sails, Waterline, Sequelize ORM, OAuth, Google and Apple messaging NodeJS, Mocha, SinonJS, JSHint, Git, pdepend AMQP (RabbitMQ), supervisord, DNode, Redis Eclipse, Sublime Text, Bash and friends  See testimonial by Andrew Balfour</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hindin Solutions</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-hindinsolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-hindinsolutions/</guid>
      <description> Architectural Consulting and Development
    Provided Architectural and Development guidance to the:
 Development Manager Development Lead Development Team  Mentoring all.    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pivot Software</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-pivotsoftware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-pivotsoftware/</guid>
      <description> Architectural Consulting
    Provided architectural guidance specifically around JavaScript framework decisions to the development lead.    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King&#39;s Church</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-kingschurch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-kingschurch/</guid>
      <description> Security Assessment
    Provided Security Assessment following a responsible disclosure.
 Liaised with trusties and vendors Provided education and mentoring     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christchurch City Council</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-ccc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-ccc/</guid>
      <description>Integration Development
    Integrated some of our cities public organisations into the Christchurch City Council&#39;s work flow. Liaising with Architects, development teams from CCC, City Care and others to achieve the optimum result.
Mentoring all involved.
Common Technologies: C#, WCF    See testimonials by Ming Yii and Engela Pretorius</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engela Pretorius</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-engela-pretorius/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-engela-pretorius/</guid>
      <description>System Analyst, Christchurch City Council
 Kim has an excellent work ethic and always keeps the bigger picture in mind.
His recommendations added value to the final solution.
Appreciated his diligence to unravel a difficult process and make it work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ming Yii</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-ming-yii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-ming-yii/</guid>
      <description>Team Leader, Software Engineering Team, Christchurch City Council
 2 words to describe Kim – mystery &amp;#38; legend.
Mystery – Kim is deep &amp;#38; smart. He sees things differently, from several angles &amp;#38; is full of ideas. You never know what he will suggest, and will be surprised with how he tackles issues with the solutions that he has.
Legend – Throw anything to him, no matter how twisted and broken they are, and Kim will sort them out, with</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glen Senior</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-glen-senior/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-glen-senior/</guid>
      <description>Owner, TSBC
 Kim set up a huge legacy at TSBC by implementing Scrum across our dev, and the transparency I&amp;rsquo;ve had in the last few months is a testament to his passion for our work, and his dedication to having the interests of the business a priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joe Kearns</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-joe-kearns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-joe-kearns/</guid>
      <description>Principal Consultant - Agile | Lean at Double-O Consultants
 I&amp;rsquo;ve had the pleasure of managing Kim and have found him to be a highly-focused and very skilled software developer. He works hard to ensure he achieves high quality in everything he develops and always has his employer&amp;rsquo;s interests at heart.
He wants to achieves great results and will drive himself and others around him to achieve this. Any organisation Kim is involved with will benefit immensely from his involvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Pinamonti</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-james-pinamonti/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/testimonial-james-pinamonti/</guid>
      <description>Solution Delivery Team Leader at IAG New Zealand
 I have worked with Kim as a colleague and as one of his Scrum Masters on projects including application integration, ASP.Net, Windows Workflow Foundation and Windows Communications Foundation. Kim is not only knowledgeable and passionate about software design and development, but also assertive in his approach to providing the best solution in the first instance. I believe Kim would be beneficial to any project he was a member.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>