<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>organisational-security-service | BinaryMist</title>
    <link>https://binarymist.io/tags/organisational-security-service/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://binarymist.io/tags/organisational-security-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>organisational-security-service</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2018 BinaryMist Ltd</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://binarymist.io/media/sharing.png</url>
      <title>organisational-security-service</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/tags/organisational-security-service/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Strategy Retainer $3495NZ &#43; GST</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/service-security-strategy-retainer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/service-security-strategy-retainer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not sure of how secure your business assets are?
Maybe you are thinking about establishing a security roadmap or checkpoints, but unsure of where to start, or which step to take next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may already be on the information security journey, but need some reassurance and clear direction along the way that you are investing in the areas that are most cost effective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are ways to significantly reduce the costs of security, even use security as a positive marketing avenue. Customers love it when they know you&amp;rsquo;re taking the security of their data seriously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe you build software in-house and your development team(s) could do with some assistance and a sounding board to bounce their security related questions off?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or maybe you have customers that entrust their personal data to you to manage and store in the Cloud?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;how-it-works&#34;&gt;How it works&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our agreement entitles you to unlimited 24/7 access to Kim via phone, SMS, email, Slack, Skype, Signal, Telegram, or other Instant Messaging service. I return all messages no later than the next business day, although in practice response time is usually much quicker (particularly between 9am to 6pm NZT, but also nights and weekends).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meetings are scheduled in advance, typically take place over the phone, and are sometimes supplemented with on-line meeting and/or screen sharing software (e.g. Google Hangouts, appear.in, Skype, etc).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are several possible areas of involvement:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regular meetings with the primary project contact to discuss strategy, longer-term issues, and business goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strategic and tactical advice based on a series of ongoing meetings with team leaders. These are individualised and mutually agreed upon. In addition, I&amp;rsquo;ll serve as a sounding board as they work to achieve their business and technical goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical review of architecture, work-flows, source code, documentation, and the like. Where appropriate, I&amp;rsquo;ll provide code samples, or proof-of-concept examples. Please note that authoring shipping code, designs, or documentation is not included in this agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Situational responsiveness to needs that arise that you deem require my assistance, which are not covered elsewhere.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our fee covers four months, we arrange and pay for any necessary administrative expenses such as discussed communication mediums. Professional courtesy discounts are available for recurring annual arrangements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;reserve-your-consultation&#34;&gt;Reserve Your Consultation&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Currently we have availability for select new clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-outline-primary&#34; href=&#34;https://binarymist.io/#contact&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reserve Your Confidential Consultation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;img class=&#34;testimonial-img-bordered&#34; src=&#34;../testimonial-peter-montgomery/featured.jpg&#34;&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-inventorytech&#34;&gt;Founder and CEO, InventoryTech Limited&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kim provided us with excellent support services during a development transition with our cloud software services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kim is a highly capable software developer with deep experience and capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recommend Kim&amp;rsquo;s services, he did a great job for us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;reserve-your-consultation-1&#34;&gt;Reserve Your Consultation&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Currently we have availability for select new clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-outline-primary&#34; href=&#34;https://binarymist.io/#contact&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reserve Your Confidential Consultation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participation is extremely limited. You can elect to be added to the waiting list if spots are not available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Review, Penetration Testing</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/project/service-security-review-penetration-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/project/service-security-review-penetration-testing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;situation&#34;&gt;Situation&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your software project is at the stage where you would like some verification that it is going to be able to resist attacks from your likely attackers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have deployed your project to the Cloud and need some confirmation that the infrastructure is configured correctly so that your attackers can not compromise your customers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Docker containers can be a god send for creating micro-service architectures, but often Docker environments are insecure by default.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your Software Engineers are building networks by way of infrastructure as code (IaC). These networks need security review and sometimes penetration testing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;we-can-do-better&#34;&gt;We can do better&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Would you like peace of mind that your software project is going to be able to withstand the likely attacks from your adversaries?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Achieving and maintaining a level of security with your cloud configuration, security rules and settings can be a daunting task. Would you like to be able to relax and be confident that this is taken care of?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Securing your micro-service and Docker environments is not for the faint hearted, this is an area that Kim has a wealth of experience in. You too can share the same knowledge that your micro-service and Docker environments are &lt;a href=&#34;https://binarymist.io/publication/docker-security/&#34;&gt;well secured&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the knowledge and experience that we have with cloud environments and tools such as Terraform, Ansible, etc, you can rest assured that the networks your Engineers are creating are configured correctly, and will resist the attempts of your attackers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-we-can-help&#34;&gt;How we can help&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although we advocate bringing the security focus &lt;a href=&#34;https://binarymist.io/project/service-development-team-security-implementation/&#34;&gt;up front&lt;/a&gt; where it&amp;rsquo;s the cheapest to implement, we understand that this is a journey that takes time. Ultimately our aim is to help you get there, but in the interim, we can work with you by reviewing, testing and establishing a solid security stature across your market offerings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can review, penetration test, evaluate costs and trade-offs, provide a custom report outlining the defects and effective mitigations. Then work with your development team(s) to help them understand the issues and how to apply the mitigations themselves, thus aiding recognition of future defects as they&amp;rsquo;re introduced, saving large amounts of rework. We can also simply fix the defects for you if that&amp;rsquo;s your preference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can traverse the minefield of your cloud environment with you. Locate, document, and work with your Engineers helping them to rectify the security issues in your cloud deployments, or apply the necessary remedies for you and your teams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Network security is an area that Kim has been actively engaged in designing, building and breaking for many years. We can work with you supplying valuable knowledge and experience to your project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let us review, test, and provide the peace of mind that your market offerings will withstand the attacks from your adversaries&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;reserve-your-consultation&#34;&gt;Reserve Your Consultation&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Currently we have availability for select new clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-outline-primary&#34; href=&#34;https://binarymist.io/#contact&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reserve Your Confidential Consultation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the sensitive nature of these engagements, they are not usually added to our portfolio, but you can see&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-our-customers-are-saying&#34;&gt;What our customers are saying&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stefan Streichsbier&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img class=&#34;testimonial-img-bordered&#34; src=&#34;../testimonial-stefan-streichsbier/featured.jpg&#34;&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://binarymist.io/project/portfolio-numisec&#34;&gt;Numisec Pte. Ltd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve met Kim at DevSecCon Singapore in 2017 where he gave a well-received &lt;a href=&#34;https://binarymist.io/event/devseccon-asia-2017-workshop-developing-a-high-perf-security-focussed-agile-team/&#34;&gt;workshop&lt;/a&gt;. A few months later we had a project where his top-notch strong &lt;strong&gt;Node.js security&lt;/strong&gt; code review skills were required and this gave us the chance to work together closely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over a 2 week period he was doing security code reviews of containerized Node.js &lt;strong&gt;microservices&lt;/strong&gt; in a very thorough way. We communicated well and progressed quickly. Kim has a very broad yet deep understanding of modern application security that comes from years of experience. I can recommend Kim to anyone who needs an &lt;a href=&#34;https://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap06.html#web-applications&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;application security&lt;/a&gt; expert and wants a professional second opinion on the security posture of an application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kim has spent significant effort in researching &lt;a href=&#34;https://binarymist.io/publication/docker-security/&#34;&gt;Docker security&lt;/a&gt;, how to determine insecure environments, configurations, how to provide countermeasures, and has &lt;a href=&#34;https://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap03.html#vps-identify-risks-docker&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;written&lt;/a&gt; on the topic &lt;a href=&#34;https://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap03.html#vps-countermeasures-docker&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;extensively&lt;/a&gt;. Kim has also liaised with and &lt;a href=&#34;https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-docker-security/&#34;&gt;interviewed&lt;/a&gt; the Docker Security Team Lead, and is well equipped to address and rectify any security issues you may have with Docker environments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    BinaryMist project leveraging Docker and Terraform to create free and secure networking components:
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/binarymist/aws-docker-host&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://github.com/binarymist/aws-docker-host/raw/master/Logo.png&#34; alt=&#34;AWS Docker Host&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kim has also detailed some of his network knowledge in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://f1.holisticinfosecforwebdevelopers.com/chap04.html#network&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Network chapter&lt;/a&gt; of his second book, along with &lt;a href=&#34;https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-network-security/&#34;&gt;interview&lt;/a&gt; of network security guru Haroon Meer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because Kim has spent many years in development and engineering, as well as performing security reviews and penetration tests, he brings a unique and holistic view of what is required from both sides (defence and attack), being able to work with your team(s) to provide effective and realistic simulations of real-world attacks, at the same time, coaching your developers what to look for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;reserve-your-consultation-1&#34;&gt;Reserve Your Consultation&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Currently we have availability for select new clients.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-outline-primary&#34; href=&#34;https://binarymist.io/#contact&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reserve Your Confidential Consultation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the nature of this type of work, we can only take on one new client per month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
