<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on BinaryMist</title>
    <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on BinaryMist</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 BinaryMist Ltd &lt;/br&gt;Following images are used under Creative Commons: [1](https://www.flickr.com/photos/ravefinity/12180959354/in/photostream/) &lt;/br&gt;[Privacy](/publication/privacy/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://binarymist.io/publication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Natalie Silvanovich on Attack Surface Reduction</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-attack-surface-reduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-attack-surface-reduction/</guid>
      <description>This show has been recorded, but is yet to be relealsed.
 Show Outline Basic Questions  Can you explain what attack surface is? If we are to reduce attack surface, we need to be able to measure it. How would you go about quantifying the attack surface before and after defects have been found and fixed? How does your threat modelling approach take into consideration the severity as well as number of defects?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Security - Quick Reference</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/cloud-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/cloud-security/</guid>
      <description>The book also covers:
 Techniques and tools for storing and accessing secrets in the Cloud securely Risks and countermeasures of serverless offerings Infrastructure and configuration management techniques and tools An interview with Scott Piper (AWS security specialist) Many other tips, tricks and tools  
Please note that the entire content of this book is included in The Cloud chapter of Holistic InfoSec for Web Developers F1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Péter Budai on End to End Encryption</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-end-to-end-encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-end-to-end-encryption/</guid>
      <description>Show Outline Basic Questions  What is end-to-end encryption?
(plain text -&amp;gt; cipher text. If there are intermediaries, they can not make sense of the data) Why do we need end-to-end encryption, what’s the goal here?
(One example would be a European organisation which stores its archived data off-site in the USA. Under the terms of the USA PATRIOT Act, American authorities can demand access to all data physically stored within its boundaries, even if it includes personal information on European citizens with no connections to the USA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scott Piper on Cloud Security</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-cloud-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-cloud-security/</guid>
      <description>This show made it into the VertitechIT list of Best IT Podcasts for 2018.
This is the second show Kim has hosted that&amp;rsquo;s made it into this list.
 &amp;nbsp;
Show Outline Basic Questions  When moving to the Cloud, our servers/compute, storage, and many other physical aspects have now become abstract concepts. As a Software Engineer, what thoughts do you have on how we need to change our approach to security when moving to the cloud?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Security - Quick Reference</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/docker-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/docker-security/</guid>
      <description> Check out Kim&amp;rsquo;s blog post which goes into some of the detail within this book, along with what others are saying about Docker Security.

Please note that the entire content of this book is included in The VPS chapter of Holistic InfoSec for Web Developers F1.

Errata (errors, typos, etc.)  Submit an issue Open issues Closed issues  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kim&#39;s Books</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/kims-selected-publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/kims-selected-publications/</guid>
      <description>Cloud Security &amp;nbsp; - &amp;nbsp; Quick Reference &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Providing insight into the shared responsibility model of the Cloud. Making sure your security stature in the Cloud is where you need it to be? Providing the architectural and technical direction required to create your secure Cloud environment. This entire content is included in The VPS chapter of Holistic InfoSec for Web Developers F1.
     Docker Security &amp;nbsp; - &amp;nbsp; Quick Reference &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The security defaults of Docker are established to get you up and running (“just work”) quickly, rather than being the most secure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holistic Info-Sec for Web Developers</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/holistic-infosec-for-web-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/holistic-infosec-for-web-developers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zane Lackey on Application Security</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-application-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-application-security/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre Conference Interview</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/alldaydevops2017-interview-secrets-of-a-high-performance-security-focussed-agile-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/alldaydevops2017-interview-secrets-of-a-high-performance-security-focussed-agile-team/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haroon Meer on Network Security</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-network-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-network-security/</guid>
      <description>Show Outline Basic Questions  What is network security? What is application security? Just as with any other form of security, the first thing we need to think about is, what’s valuable to us in regards to network security, what are we attempting to protect and why? One of the comments I received recently was “as a software engineer, do I really care about physical network security” Why should Software Engineers care?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diogo Mónica on Docker Security</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-docker-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-docker-security/</guid>
      <description>Show Outline Basic Questions Can you give a quick explanation of how Docker containers work for our listeners?
If you were an attacker looking to compromise Docker, knowing what the weakest areas are, where would you start and what would be your first targets in terms of the surrounding technologies?
&amp;nbsp;
I’m going to address each of the areas in turn, you mentioned a while ago, that we should address&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kim&#39;s Career Story</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/javascriptjabber-interview-kims-career-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/javascriptjabber-interview-kims-career-story/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Francois Raynaud on DevSecOps</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-devsecops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-devsecops/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neil Ford on Success Skills for Architects</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-success-skills-for-architects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/ser-podcast-success-skills-for-architects/</guid>
      <description>Show Outline Success Skills  In your own words, what is a software architect? How do the required skills change from the roles of Engineering to Architecture? What are the top 4 skills required to be the best Software Architect anyone can be? How have these changed over the last few years and how do you see them changing over the next 5 &amp;amp; 10 years? What do you think about the idea that Architects are born predisposed with a special set of attributes?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InfoSec for Developers</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/dotnetrocks-interview-infosec-for-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/dotnetrocks-interview-infosec-for-developers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/privacy/</guid>
      <description>BinaryMist Privacy Statement 
The Short Version We collect your statistics only with your consent. We only collect the minimum amount of personal information required to understand the purpose of your interactions with this website. This information as far as we are aware will not be sold to third parties.
For more information read the below.
Analytics We are using Google Analytics (GA) as a third party tracking service. We do not use it to track you individually or collect personal information about you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kali Linux Review</title>
      <link>https://binarymist.io/publication/pentest-magazine-kali-linux-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarymist.io/publication/pentest-magazine-kali-linux-review/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>